Guide to the Marvin Mirsky Papers 1941-2014
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: Literature
  - Mann, Thomas, notes, articles, 1950-1974 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Mann, Thomas, notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Mann, Thomas, bibliography, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Mantel, Hilary, Bring Up the Bodies, notes, articles, 2012-2013 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Marai, Sandor, Casanova in Bolzano, notes, articles, 2005-2006 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Marai, Sandor, Embers, notes, articles, 2001-2004 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Mason, Bobbie Ann, In Country, notes, articles, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Mason, Zachary, The Last Books of the Odyssey, notes, articles, 2010-2011 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - McCann, Colum, Let the World Spin, notes, articles, 2009-2010 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - McCarthy, Cormac, All the Pretty Horses, notes, articles, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - McCarthy, Cormac, The Crossing, notes, articles, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - McCarthy, Cormac, No Country for Old Men, notes, articles, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - McCarthy, Cormac, The Road, notes, articles, 2006-2007 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - McEwan, Ian, Amsterdam, notes, articles, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - McEwan, Ian, Atonement, notes, articles, 2001-2003 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - McEwan, Ian, Enduring Love, notes, articles, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - McEwan, Ian, Saturday, notes, articles, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - McEwan, Ian, Solar, notes, articles, 2009-2011 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Melville, Herman, Moby Dick, notes, articles, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Menzies, Gavin, 1434, articles, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Milton, John, Paradise Lost, notes, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Moliere, Tartuffe, notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Morrison, Toni, A Mercy, articles, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Morrison, Toni, Home, notes, articles, 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Morrison, Toni, Jazz, notes, articles, 1981-1992 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Morrison, Toni, Love, notes, articles, 2004-2005 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Morrison, Toni, Paradise, notes, articles, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Mo Yan, Red Sorghum, notes, articles, 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Muller, Herta, The Appointment, notes, articles, 2009-2011 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Muller, Herta, The Hunger Angel, notes, articles, 2012 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Munro, Alice, The Love of a Good Woman, notes, articles, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Murakami, Haruki, After Dark, notes, articles, 2008-2009 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Murakami, Haruki, IQ84, notes, articles, 2011-2012 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Murakami, Haruki, Kafka on the Shore, notes, articles, 1999-2006 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Murakami, Haruji, Norwegian Wood, notes, articles, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Murakami, Haruji, Sputnik Sweetheart, notes, articles, 2000-2002 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Musil, Robert, The Man Without Qualities, Vol. 1, notes, articles, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Nabokov, Vladimir, notes, articles, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Nafisi, Azar, Reading Lolita in Tehran, notes, articles, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Naipaul, V. S., Half a Life, notes, articles, 1999-2003 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Naipaul, V. S., Magic Seeds, notes, articles, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Nemirovsky, Irene, Suite Francaise, notes, articles, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - O’Brien, Tim, The Things They Carried, notes, articles, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Oe, Kenzaburo, Teach Us to Outgrow Our Madness, notes, articles, 1993-1995 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Ondaatje, Michael, Anil’s Ghost, notes, articles, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Ondaatje, Michael, Divisadero, notes, articles, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Ondaatje, Michael, The English Patient, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Oz, Amos, To Know a Woman, notes, articles, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Pamuk, Orhan, The Museum of Innocence, notes, articles, 2008-2011 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Pamuk, Orhan, Snow, notes, articles, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Philips, Jayne Anne, Shelter, notes, articles, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Phillips, Arthur, The Tragedy of Arthur, notes, articles, 2011-2013 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Pinckney, Daryl, High Cotton, notes, articles, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Pinter, Harold, notes, articles, playbills, 1963-1980 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Plato, Euthyphro; Apology; Crito; Protagoras, notes, paper assignment, 1979-1991 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Plato, Meno, book, notes, paper assignment, articles, 1959-1991 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Plato, Meno, translation copies, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Plato, Meno, correspondence, notes, text, 1983-1991 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Plato, The Republic, notepad, notes, article, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Proulx, E. Annie, The Shipping News, notes, articles, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Proust, Marcel, In Search of Lost Time, articles, correspondence, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Proust, Marcel, Remembrance of Things Past, articles, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Proust, Marcel, notes, 1983-1985 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Pye, Michael, Pieces from Berlin, notes, articles, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Pynchon, Thomas, The Crying of Lot 49, notes, articles, 1966-2003 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Pynchon, Thomas, Gravity’s Rainbow, notes, articles, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Pynchon, Thomas, Inherent Vice, notes, articles, 2009-2010 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Pynchon, Thomas, Mason & Dixon, articles, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Pynchon, Thomas, Vineland, notes, articles, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Rhys, Jean, Wide Sargasso Sea, notes, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Robinson, Marilynne, Gilead, notes, articles, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Roth, Henry, An American Type, notes, articles, 2010-2011 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Roth, Henry, Call it Sleep, notes, articles, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Roth, Henry, Mercy of a Rude Stream: Vol. I: A Star Shines Over Mt. Morris Park, notes, articles, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Roth, Joseph, The Radetzky March, notes, articles, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Roth, Philip, American Pastoral, article, undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Roth, Philip, The Anatomy Lesson, notes, articles, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Roth, Philip, The Counterlife, notes, articles, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Roth, Philip, Everyman, notes, articles, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Roth, Philip, Exit Ghost, notes, articles, 2007-2008 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Roth, Philip, The Facts, articles, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Roth, Philip, The Ghost Writer, notes, articles, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Roth, Philip, Goodbye, Columbus; My Life As a Man, notes, article, 1959-1974 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Roth, Philip, The Human Stain, notes, articles, 1997-2000 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Roth, Philip, I Married a Communist, notes, articles, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Roth, Philip, Indignation, notes, articles, 2008-2010 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Roth, Philip, Nemesis, notes, articles, 2010-2011 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Roth, Philip, Operation Shylock, notes, articles, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Roth, Philip, Patrimony, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Roth, Philip, Sabbath’s Theatre, notes, articles, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Roth Philip, Zuckerman Unbound; Zuckerman Bound, notes, articles, 1981-1985 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Roy, Arundhati, The God of Small Things, notes, articles, 1995-1997 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Rush, Norman, Mating, notes, articles, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Rushdie, Salman, East, West (Stories), notes, articles, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Rushdie, Salman, The Enchantress of Florence, notes, articles, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Rushdie, Salman, Fury, notes, articles, 2001-2003 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Rushdie, Salman, The Ground Beneath Her Feet, notes, articles, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Rushdie, Salman, Haroun and the Sea of Stories, notes, articles, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Rushdie, Salman, The Moor’s Last Sigh, notes, articles, 1995-1997 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Rushdie, Salman, The Satanic Verses, notes, articles, 1989-2002 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Rushdie, Salman, The Satanic Verses, articles, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Rushdie, Salman, Shalimar the Clown, notes, articles, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Salinger, J.D., The Catcher in the Rye, notes, articles, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Saramago, Jose, Baltasar and Blimunda, notes, articles, 1988-2003 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Saramago, Jose, Blindness, notes, articles, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Sebald, W.G., Austerlitz, notes, articles, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Sebald, W.G., The Rings of Saturn, notes, articles, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Shakespeare, William, All’s Well that Ends Well-Hamlet, notes, articles, 1984-1991 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Shakespeare, William, Julius Caesar-Measure for Measure, notes, articles, 1988-1996 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Shakespeare, William, The Merchant of Venice-Much Ado About Nothing, notes, articles, playbill, 1929-1999 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Shakespeare, William, Othello-The Tempest, notes, 1973-1991 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Shakespeare, William, Timon of Athens-The Winter’s Tale, notes, 1978-1998 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Shakespeare, William, General Introduction, notes, articles, 1987-1997 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Shaw, George Bernard, notes, articles, 1977-1992 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Shields, Carol, The Stone Diaries, notes, articles, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Smiley, Jane, A Thousand Acres, notes, articles, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Smith, Zadie, NW, notes, articles, 2010-2013 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Smith, Zadie, On Beauty, notes, articles, 2006-2008 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Sontag, Susan, In America, notes, articles, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Sophocles, notes, articles, 1966-1981 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Stendhal, Selected Works course material, lecture notes, correspondence, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Stoppard, Tom, Arcadia, notes, articles, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Swift, Graham, The Light of Day, notes, articles, 2003-2004 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Tertz, Abram, Fantastic Stories, notes, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace, Vanity Fair, notes, articles, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Thomas, D.M., Ararat, notes, articles, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Thomas, D.M., Swallow, notes, articles, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Thomas, D.M., The White Hotel, notes, articles, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Thomas, Michael, Man Gone Down, notes, articles, 2007-2009 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Thucydides, notes, reading lists, course materials, 1977-1985 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Toibin, Colm, Brooklyn, notes, articles, 2009-2011 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Toibin, Colm, The Master, notes, articles, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Tolstoy, Leo, Anna Karenina, notes, articles, 1972-1993 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Tolstoy, Leo, War and Peace, course material, notes, articles, 1972-1982 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Tolstoy, Leo, War and Peace, notes, articles, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Tolstoy, Leo, Selected Works course material, notes, articles, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Tolstaya, Tatyana, Sleepwalker in a Fog, notes, articles, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Trollope, Anthony, Barchester Towers, notes, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Tsushima, Yuko, Child of Fortune, notes, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Twain, Mark, Huckleberry Finn, notes, examination, 1955-1989 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Updike, John, The Afterlife and Other Stories, notes, articles, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Updike, John, Bech at Bay: A Quasi-novel, notes, articles, 1998-2000 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Updike, John, Gertrude and Claudius, notes, articles, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Updike, John, In the Beauty of the Lilies, notes, articles, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Updike, John, Licks of Love, notes, articles, 2000-2002 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Updike, John, My Father’s Tears, notes, articles, 2009-2010 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Updike, John, Rabbit at Rest, notes, articles, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Updike, John, Terrorist, articles, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Updike, John, Villages, articles, 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Vargas Llosa, Mario, The Bad Girl, notes, articles, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Vargas Llosa, Mario, In Praise of the Stepmother, notes, articles, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Wallace, David Foster, The Pale King, notes, articles, 2000-2011 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Weldon, Fay, The Life and Loves of a She-Devil, notes, articles, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - West, Nathanael, The Day of the Locust, notes, articles, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Wharton, Edith, notes, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Wiggins, Marianne, John Dollar, notes, articles, 1989-1991 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Winterson, Jeanette, Art and Lies, notes, articles, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Winterson, Jeanette, Sexing the Cherry, notes, articles, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Winterson, Jeanette, Written on the Body, notes, articles, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Woolf, Virginia, The Waves, notes, articles, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Woolf, Virginia, course materials, notes, articles, 1985-2000 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Wright, Stephen, The Amalgamation Polka, notes, articles, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Xingjian, Gao, Soul Mountain, notes, articles, 2000-2002 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Yehoshua, Abraham B., Mr. Mani, notes, articles, 1992-1994 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Series II: Cinema
  - Ackermann, Joan, The Batting Cage, article, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Allen, Woody, Alice, notes, articles, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Allen, Woody, Bullets over Broadway, notes, articles, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Allen, Woody, Celebrity, notes, articles, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Allen, Woody, Crimes and Misdemeanors, notes, articles, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Allen, Woody, Husbands and Wives, notes, articles, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Allen, Woody, Shadows and Fog, notes, articles, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Allen, Woody, notes, articles, 1977-1980 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Allen, Woody, notes, articles, 1978-1988 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Altman, Robert, Gosford Park, notes, articles, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Altman, Robert, Short Cuts; The Player, notes, articles, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Amelio, Gianni, Il Ladro di Bambini (Stolen Children), notes, articles, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Anderson, Paul Thomas, Magnolia, notes, articles, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Anderson, Paul Thomas, There Will Be Blood, notes, articles, 2007-2008 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Anderson, Wes, The Royal Tenenbaums, notes, articles, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Aronofsky, Darren, Black Swan, notes, articles, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Becker, Harold, City Hall, notes, articles, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Benton, Robert, The Human Stain, notes, articles, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Bertolucci, Bernardo, The Dreamers, notes, articles, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Boyle, Danny, Slumdog Millionaire, notes, articles, 2005-2008 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Branagh, Kenneth, Hamlet, notes, articles, 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Cameron, James, Avatar, notes, articles, 2009-2010 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Campion, Jane, The Piano, notes, articles, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Coen brothers, A Serious Man, notes, articles, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Coen brothers, Fargo, notes, articles, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Coen brothers, The Man Who Wasn’t There, notes, articles, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Coen brothers, No Country for Old Men, notes, articles, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Coen brothers, True Grit, notes, articles, 2010-2011 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Daldry, Stephen, Billy Elliot, article, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Daldry, Stephen, The Hours, notes, articles, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Daldry, Stephen, The Reader, notes, articles, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Davies, Terence, The House of Mirth, notes, articles, 2000-2001 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Demme, Jonathan, Beloved, notes, articles, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - DeVito, Danny, Hoffa, notes, articles, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Duigan, John, Wide Sargasso Sea, notes, articles, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Duncan, Peter, Children of the Revolution, notes, articles, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Eastwood, Clint, Changeling, notes, articles, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Eastwood, Clint, Mystic River, notes, articles, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Eastwood, Clint, Unforgiven, notes, articles, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Fellini, Federico, articles, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Field, Todd, In the Bedroom, notes, articles, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Fincher, David, The Curious Case of Benjamin Button, notes, articles, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Fincher, David, The Social Network, notes, articles, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Garcia, Nicole, Place Vendome, article, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Ghobadi, Bahman, A Time for Drunken Horses, notes, articles, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Gray, James, The Yards, article, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Hampton, Christopher, Carrington, notes, articles, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Hicks, Scott, Shine, notes, articles, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Hillcoat, John, The Road, notes, articles, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Hood, Gavin, Rendition, notes, articles, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Hooper, Tom, The King’s Speech, notes, articles, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Hughes Brothers, The Book of Eli, notes, articles, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Ivory, James, Howards End, notes, articles, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Ivory, James, Jefferson in Paris, notes, articles, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Ivory, James, The Remains of the Day, notes, articles, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - James, Steve, Hoop Dreams, notes, articles, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Jordan, Neil, The Butcher Boy, article, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Jordan, Neil, The Crying Game, notes, articles, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Kaige, Chen, Farewell My Concubine, notes, articles, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Kieslowski, Krzysztof, Blue, notes, articles, 1991-1994 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Kieslowski, Krzysztof, Red, notes, articles, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Kurosawa, Akira, Rhapsody in August, notes, articles, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Lee, Spike, Clockers, notes, articles, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Lee, Spike, Malcolm X, notes, articles, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Leigh, Mike, Secrets and Lies, notes, articles, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Levinson, Barry, Bugsy, notes, articles, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Loncraine, Richard, Richard III, notes, articles, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Lynch, David, Mulholland Drive, notes, articles, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Madden, John, Shakespeare in Love, notes, articles, 1998-1999 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Malick, Terrence, The Thin Red Line, notes, articles, 1998-1999 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Manchevski, Milcho, Before the Rain, notes, articles, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Mann, Michael, The Insider, notes, articles, 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Mendes, Sam, American Beauty, notes, articles, 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Michell, Roger, Persuasion, notes, articles, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Minghella, Anthony, Cold Mountain, notes, articles, 2003-2004 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Minghella, Anthony, The English Patient, notes, articles, 1995-1997 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Moore, Michael, Bowling for Columbine, notes, articles, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - O’Connor, Pat, Dancing at Lughnasa, notes, articles, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Perelman, V., House of Sand and Fog, notes, articles, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Polanski, Roman, Bitter Moon, notes, articles, 1992-1994 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Polanski, Roman, The Pianist, notes, articles, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Rappeneau, Jean-Paul, The Horseman on the Roof, notes, articles, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Redford, Robert, Quiz Show, notes, articles, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Redford, Robert, A River Runs Through It, notes, articles, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Robbins, Tim, Cradle Will Rock, notes, articles, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Rohmer, Eric, Autumn Tale, notes, articles, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Rose, Bernard, Anna Karenina, notes, articles, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Rozema, Patricia, Mansfield Park, notes, articles, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Russell, David O., The Fighter, notes, articles, 2010-2011 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Ruzowitzky, Stefan, The Counterfeiters, notes, articles, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Sayles, John, Lone Star, notes, articles, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Schnabel, Julian, Basquiat, notes, articles, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Schnabel, Julian, The Diving Bell and the Butterfly, notes, articles, 2007-2008 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Scorsese, Martin, The Age of Innocence, notes, articles, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Scorsese, Martin, Bringing Out the Dead, notes, articles, 1999-2000 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Scorsese, Martin, Casino, notes, articles, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Scorsese, Martin, Gangs of New York, notes, articles, 2002-2003 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Scorsese, Martin, Shutter Island, notes, articles, 2009-2010 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Scott, Ridley, Thelma and Louise, notes, articles, 1991-1993 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Sheridan, Jim, In America, notes, articles, 2002-2004 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Spielberg, Steven, Schindler’s List, notes, articles, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Sverak, Jan, Kolya, notes, articles, 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Tarentino, Quentin, Pulp Fiction, notes, articles, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Taymor, Julie, Frida, notes, articles, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Thornton, Billy Bob, All the Pretty Horses, notes, articles, 2000-2001 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Thornton, Billy Bob, Sling Blade, notes, articles, 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Tornatore, Giuseppe, The Star Maker, notes, articles, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Ullmann, Liv, Faithless, notes, articles, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Van Sant, Gus, Milk, notes, articles, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Von Trier, Lars, Dancer in the Dark, notes, articles, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Wargnier, Regis, Indochine, notes, articles, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Wright, Joe, Atonement, notes, articles, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Zeffirelli, Franco, Jane Eyre, notes, articles, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Zhang Yimou, Ju Dou; The Story of Qiu Ju; Raise the Red Lantern, notes, articles, 1991-1993 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Zhang Yimou, To Live, notes, articles, 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Zwigoff, Terry, Crumb, notes, articles, comic strips, 1991-1995 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Series III: Course Materials
  - University of Chicago, seminars, lecture notes, 1954-1957 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - University of Chicago, course catalog selections, 1958-1959 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - University of Chicago correspondence, book requests, course proposals, 1958-1962 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - University of Chicago, Downtown Center contracts, 1958-1962 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - University of Chicago, course proposals, notes, 1980-1994 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - University of Chicago, course proposals, preliminary reading lists, 1992-1993 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - University of Chicago, Basic Program of Liberal Education for Adults, tutorial materials, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - University of Chicago, Basic Program of Liberal Education for Adults, lecture notes, informational materials, 1958-1961 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - University of Chicago, The Basic Program of Liberal Education for Adults, forms, correspondence, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - University of Chicago, Basic Program of Liberal Education for Adults, Humanities, reading lists, notes, student rosters, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - University of Chicago, Fine Arts Program, reading lists, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago, Fine Arts Program, background materials, 1957-1960 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago, Fine Arts Program, reading lists, course schedules, 1958-1961 (Box 30, Folder 3)